[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "3+5",
    "answer": "8",
    "choices": ["8", "2", "4", "6"]
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "5+7",
    "answer": "12",
    "choices": ["12", "4", "6", "10"]
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "7+9",
    "answer": "16",
    "choices": ["16", "6", "8", "14"]
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "9+11",
    "answer": "20",
    "choices": ["20", "8", "10", "18"]
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "11+13",
    "answer": "24",
    "choices": ["24", "10", "12", "22"]
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "13+15",
    "answer": "28",
    "choices": ["28", "12", "14", "26"]
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "15+17",
    "answer": "32",
    "choices": ["32", "14", "16", "30"]
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "17+19",
    "answer": "36",
    "choices": ["36", "16", "18", "34"]
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "19+21",
    "answer": "40",
    "choices": ["40", "18", "20", "38"]
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "21+23",
    "answer": "44",
    "choices": ["44", "20", "22", "42"]
  }
]